Guide to the Ben Rosen Papers, 1936-2006 and undated, bulk 1945-1991
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Business Files Series, 1946-1995 and undated, (9 boxes)
  - Scrapbooks and collected work
    - Logo designs, undated, (2 folders; 1 folder removed to Box 22) (Box 21)
    - Scrapbooks, 1946-1995
      - Scrapbook 1, (2 folders) (Box 21)
        Includes original letterhead designs for Action Council for Better Cities, Ben Rosen Associates, Horizon House/Tishman Realty, ICOA Life Insurance, J. Gordon Carr & Associates Architects, and Scully Brothers.
      - Scrapbook 2, (2 folders) (Box 21)
        Includes original letterhead designs for Ben Rosen Associates, Intermark, North American Reinsurance, Richardson-Merrell, and Ritta, Rosen & Arnoldy.
  - Oversize materials
    - Ben Rosen Associates (Box 22)
      - Administrative--House promotional brochure designs, undated (Box 22)
      - Administrative--New office announcement, Soirée, undated (Box 22)
      - New Business--Venture calendar/planner design, 2001-2002 (Box 22)
      - Publication, What in the World is Packaging All About? 1955 (Box 22)
      - Reference--Paul Stoudard calligraphy examples, undated (Box 22)
    - Ben Rosen, Designer
      - Other designs, circa 1948-1952 (Box 22)
    - Scrapbooks and collected work
      - Logo designs, undated (Box 22)
- Client Files Series, 1948-1988 and undated, bulk 1968-1988
  Contains design concepts, sketches, presentation materials/display boards, and final designs for a variety of visual communications projects, with a focus on corporate identity programs and package design. Bulk of series represents package design sketches, mock-ups, and finished products produced for clients including American Loose Leaf, CCMI/McGraw-Hill, Equitable Life Assurance, Exxon, Gilbarco (subsidiary of Exxon/Esso), IBM, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, North American Reinsurance, Philip Morris, Richardson-Vicks, Russ Berrie, and Tishman Realty and Construction. Materials also touch on Rosen's work on projects for government and public institutions, including a President Kennedy memorial document, a commemorative book for the United Nations 20th anniversary, and Rosen's submission to the World Trade Center Memorial design competition.
  - Corporate Identity Programs and Paper Records, 1948-1988 and undated
    Includes correspondence, planning documentation and designs for logos and small-format paper items such as letterheads, catalogs, corporate manuals and promotional materials.
    - AAA Automobile Club of New York, logo concepts, 1950-1951 (Box 21)
    - Almar rainwear, report and photograms, undated (Box 21)
    - American Book Company, 1967 (Box 21)
    - American Loose Leaf Company
      - Catalog, with transparencies, circa 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - Concepts/Color charts, circa 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - Construction Kit, circa 1977-1978 (Box 23)
      - Reports
        - Corporate identification and sales support program (with revisions), 1976 (Box 23)
        - Phase I: Preliminary Research Report, 1976 (Box 23)
    - Asgrow Mandeville (pre-seeded planters)
      - Planter box design memo, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Preliminary report (draft), circa early 1970s (Box 23)
      - Proposal/Recommendations report, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Axces, logo concepts, undated (Box 23)
    - CCMI McGraw-Hill
      - Binders
        - Call Pricer (PC software for long-distance service selections), circa 1982-1986, (2 folders) (Box 23)
        - Master Planning Guide
          - Inserts, circa 1985-1986 (Box 23)
          - Promotion (concept sketches, final advertising with photos of binders), circa 1985-1986 (Box 23)
          - Three-binder final version, circa 1985-1986 (Box 24)
        - Planning Guide X-1: A Compact Guide to InterLATA Telecommunications Rates and Services, 1983 (Box 24)
        - Q-Tel 1000, circa 1982-1986 (Box 25)
      - Folders, circa 1982-1986 (Box 25)
      - Letterhead, circa 1985 (Box 25)
      - Newsletter designs
        - At the LATA level: The Only News Digest of Telecommunciations Activities on a State-to-State Basis, 1985 (Box 25)
        - Impact: Analysis of Communication Common Carrier Changes and Competitive Offerings, 1985 (Box 25)
        - This Month in Telecommunication: Monthly News Digest of Key Data Communications and Telephony Events (designs/direct mail/promotion), 1985, (3 folders) (Box 25)
        - Newsletter logos/promotion, circa 1985 (Box 25)
      - Project proposal (timetable, financials, rough sketches), 1985 (Box 25)
    - Check Card Systems, visual identity program, report and notes, 1969-1971 (Box 25)
    - Coats and Clark, Learn How to Crochet book design/content (sketches, concepts, reports), 1957-1958 (Box 25)
    - Consumers Union Report on Family Planning (Alan Guttmacher and Editors of Consumer Reports), 1962, (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Cushing & Nevell (industrial designers) Design Procedure manual, 1958 (Box 25)
    - Della Torre, Julie, Storyteller logo designs, 1995 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Dinalon (Swiss nail polish), promotional cards, undated (Box 25)
    - DSD, Informatics Design Guide/Graphic Standards, 1974 (Box 25)
    - Eastern Airlines, corporate identity redesign reference manual, 1965-1966 and undated (Box 25)
    - E. Ingraham Co. (Dreyfus), clock and watch dials, 1950 (Box 25)
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, promotional materials, undated, (4 folders; 1 folder removed to Box 61.) (Box 25)
    - Exxon, corporate identification program (Box 26)
      - Candidates
        - Correspondence, 1977-1978 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 26)
        - List of candidates/timetables, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
        - Professional group lists (AIGA, PDC), 1972-1977 and undated (Box 26)
        - Selection forms, circa 1978 (Box 26)
      - Consultant contracts and objectives (Ben Rosen Associates), 1977-1980 and undated (Box 26)
      - Correspondence regarding presentations, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
      - Design firms
        - Appraisal form, undated (Box 26)
        - Presentation notes, 1978 (Box 26)
      - Design program
        - Booklet, Exxon Marketing Exchange, 1981 Fall (Box 26)
        - Contract and terms, 1980 (Box 26)
        - Contractor files (Saul Bass/Herb Yaeger and Associates)
          - Binders, 1978-1981, (8 folders) (Box 26)
          - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 26)
          - Design Standards Manual, undated, (4 folders) (Box 27)
          - Reports, 1981 (Box 27)
      - Designer proposals
        - Abraham Rothenberg Associates, undated (Box 27)
        - Alan Y. Taniguchi FAIA and Associates, 1977 (Box 27)
        - Anspach Grossman Portugal, Inc., 1978, (3 folders) (Box 27)
        - Byron Osterweil Associates, 1977 (Box 27)
        - Chajet Design Group, 1977, (2 folders; 1 folder removed to Box 61.) (Box 27)
        - Cuccio Chieda & Bell, 1978 (Box 27)
        - David Chapman Design, 1978 (Box 27)
        - Design Research Unit, undated (Box 27)
        - Fujita Design, 1977 (Box 27)
        - Gerstman-Meyers, Inc., 1977 (Box 27)
        - Gregory Fossella Associates, 1977 (Box 28)
        - Hunter Straker Templeton Limited, undated (Box 28)
        - Landor Associates, 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 28)
        - Lou Dorfsman, Inc., undated (Box 28)
        - Luth & Katz, 1977 (Box 28)
        - Murtha, DeSola, Finsilver, Fiore, Inc., 1977, (2 folders) (Box 28)
        - Pentagram, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 28)
        - Racila & Vallarta Associates, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 28)
        - Sandgren Associates, 1977 (Box 28)
        - Saul Bass/Herb Yaeger & Associates, undated (Box 28)
        - Schechter Group, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 28)
        - Siegel & Gale, 1977 (Box 28)
        - Stewart & Morrison, Ltd., 1977, (2 folders) (Box 29)
        - Unimark International, 1977 (Box 29)
      - [ Esso Identification Guide, 1965; removed to Box 61.] (Box 29)
      - Expense reports, 1977 and undated (Box 29)
      - Exxon background reports, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
      - Name Development Project
        - Preliminary presentation/correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 29)
        - Preliminary progress report, 1982 (Box 29)
        - Reports and notes, 1982 (Box 29)
      - Office Systems, reports and presentations, 1981 and undated (Box 29)
      - Presentation, Report on Search for a Design Firm, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 29)
      - Press releases, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
      - Prospectus, 1977 Nov. (Box 29)
      - Report drafts and correspondence, 1978 (Box 29)
      - Summary statements, circa late 1970s (Box 29)
    - Food Fair Stores
      - Cheq-List, 1973 (Box 29)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 29)
      - Coupons and advertisements, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
      - Pantry Pride Monthly Planner, circa 1973 (Box 29)
      - Presentation, 1973 and undated (Box 30)
    - GAF, product catalog, 1975 (Box 30)
    - Gilbarco
      - Corporate logo/typeface, 1968 (Box 30)
      - Fleet fueling, retail systems identification programs, 1981-1982 (Box 30)
      - Mailings and signage designs, undated (Box 30)
      - Press release, undated (Box 30)
      - Promotion, undated (Box 30)
      - Slide presentation script, circa 1968 (Box 30)
      - Typography, circa 1968 (Box 30)
      - Visual identity program, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Green Mountain Marble Co., logo concepts, undated (Box 30)
    - IBM
      - 632 model brochure concept, Why Use Two. Now One Will Do, undated (Box 30)
      - Promotional brochures, 1956-1960 and undated (Box 30)
    - ICOA Life Insurance Company, policy brochure and logo, undated (Box 30)
    - Informatics, user manuals, 1974 (Box 30)
    - International Standard Brands, design guide, 1970 (Box 30)
    - J. Gordon Carr & Associates, informational booklet, 1956 (Box 30)
    - Jersey Millwork Company, brochures, 1967 (Box 30)
    - John F. Kennedy memorial
      - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 30)
      - [Memorial document, 1964: removed to Box 62.] (Box 30)
        Consists of a mounted copy of Kennedy's Inaugural Address.
    - John H. Muller Associates, brochures, circa 1970s (Box 30)
    - Kasandra (tarot card/palm reader), logo concepts, circa 1987, (3 folders; 1 folder removed to Box 62.) (Box 30)
    - Key Query, logo concepts, undated (Box 30)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1956-1970 and undated, (1-3 of 9 folders) (Box 30)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1956-1970 and undated (continued), (4-9 of 9 folders; 1 folder removed to Box 62.) (Box 31)
    - [Morgan Press Collection at the Smithsonian, circa 1989], (4 folders, removed to Box 62.) (Box 31)
    - National Aniline Division, Allied Chemical
      - Organic chemical data book, 1958 (Box 31)
      - Pharmaceutical catalog, 1955 (Box 31)
    - North American Reinsurance Corporation (Box 32)
      - Advertising campaign and collateral materials, 1975-1976 (Box 32)
      - Binder cover designs, undated (Box 32)
      - Corporate identity program materials, 1975-1978 (Box 32)
      - Holiday card, undated (Box 32)
      - Mailer, Don't Call Us, undated (Box 32)
      - Presentation, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Philip Morris
      - Graphic Standards Manual, 1971 (Box 32)
      - [Posters, undated; removed to Box 62.] (Box 32)
      - Publications
        - 1%, 1967 (Box 32)
        - Alfred E. Lynn 80th birthday book, 1966 (Box 32)
        - Annual Review of the Cigarette Industry, 1970 (Box 32)
        - Business Review, 1969 (Box 32)
        - Call for Philip Morris, undated (Box 32)
          Tribute to Johnny Roventini, Philip Morris' bellboy icon.
        - Call News newsletter, 1966, (3 folders; 2 folders removed to Box 62.) (Box 32)
        - Ciga-rithmetic, 1971 (Box 32)
        - Operations Center, undated (Box 33)
        - This is Philip Morris, circa 1964 (Box 33)
          Booklet design received an award from AIGA.
        - Who's Minding Your Store, 1969 (Box 33)
      - Unified design program presentation, 1968 (Box 33)
    - Richardson-Vicks (formerly Richardson-Merrill)
      - Application forms and folders, 1981 and undated (Box 33)
      - Benefits Brief, circa 1979 (Box 33)
      - Dental assistance plan, 1981 and 1986 (Box 33)
      - Employee benefit program binder designs, circa 1981 (Box 33)
      - Employee handbook, circa 1981 (Box 33)
      - Employee savings plan, 1984 and 1986 (Box 33)
      - Health insurance plan (Box 33)
      - Income protection program, 1981 (Box 33)
      - Individual retirement options trust plan, 1988 (Box 33)
      - Life insurance program, 1981 (Box 33)
      - Major medical, post-65 plan, 1988 (Box 33)
      - Publications
        - Consumer Products Gazette, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
        - Data Book, 1972-1974 (Box 34)
        - dialog magazine, 1983-1985 (Box 34)
      - Relocation benefits brochure designs, circa 1981, (4 folders) (Box 34)
      - Retirement plan, 1984 and 1986 (Box 34)
      - Richardson-Merrill benefits brochures, 1979-1981 and undated (Box 34)
    - Russ Berrie & Co. (toys)
      - Logo button, undated (Box 34)
      - Pilot Study Report: Beginning of Phase I - Corporate Identity Program, 1978 Apr. (Box 34)
      - Presentation by Ritta, Rosen & Arnoldy (design/marketing recommendations), circa 1978 (Box 34)
    - Scully Brothers, logo concepts, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Shell Oil, logo concepts, 1948 (Box 34)
    - Sky Chef, airline menu concepts, undated (Box 34)
    - Sleep Sofas, etc., report on observations, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Standard Brands, Festival logo concepts, circa early 1970s (Box 34)
    - Third Avenue Hardware Company, logo concepts, undated (Box 34)
    - Tishman Realty and Construction Co., Inc.
      - Annual reports, 1962 and 1964 (Box 34)
      - Brochure, A Builder's Story, 1960s (Box 34)
    - United Nations Association, UN 20 commemorative book, 1965, (4 folders) (Box 34)
  - Package Designs and Layout Models, 1977-1978 and undated
    - American Loose Leaf Company, architectural model, headquarters replacement sign, circa 1977-1978 (Box 35)
    - Art Crayon Company, watercolor set, undated (Box 35)
    - Asgrow Mandeville, pre-seeded planters, undated (Box 35)
    - Asgrow Mandeville, pre-seeded planters, undated (continued) (Box 36-38)
    - Barton Candy Company, holiday box, undated (Box 39)
    - Creative Tools, Easydriver screwdriver set, undated (Box 39)
    - Dorset Laboratories (Box 40)
      - Dorset Mills Bees' Wax, undated (Box 40)
      - Clear Sight 20/20 lens cleaner, undated (Box 40)
      - Furniture Polish for Antiques, undated (Box 40)
      - Gingivite (gum treatment), undated (Box 40)
      - Heavy Duty Feminine Hand Cleaner, undated (Box 40)
    - Exxon/Esso
      - Exxon Office Systems headquarters sign, undated (Box 40)
      - Super Premium Motor Oil, one-quart cans, undated (Box 41-43)
    - IBM, 632 promotional cube, undated (Box 44)
    - International Standard Brands
      - Flan Royal, undated (Box 44)
      - Royal Baking powder, undated (Box 44)
      - Royal Gelatin, undated (Box 44)
    - Montclair Imports, Inc. (Box 45)
      - Clairmont hair brush, undated (Box 45)
      - Dinalon nail care set, undated (Box 45)
      - Montclair Imperial hair brush, undated (Box 45)
      - Royal Sweden hair brush, undated (Box 45)
    - Multiple brands, baking soda packaging (Box 45)
      Includes A&P, Food Town, Shoprite, and Waldbaum brands.
    - Philip Morris
      - Cigarette packaging (Box 4-486)
      - Cigarette, tobacco and chewing gum packaging, undated (Box 49)
    - Tishman Realty and Construction, Horizon House sign model, undated (Box 49)
  - Presentations, Sketches and Architectural Models, 1960-1984 and undated
    Primarily large format materials used for design presentations, working drawings, and three-dimensional architectural models.
    - American Loose Leaf (Box 50)
      - Architectural models (three-dimensional)
        - Folding trade show booth, circa 1977-1978 (Box 50)
        - Varick Street showroom, circa 1977-1978 (Box 50)
      - Presentation boards (Box 51)
        - Binder floor rack concepts, circa 1977-1978 (Box 51)
        - Corporate building/structure, circa 1977-1978 (Box 51)
        - Letterhead/Forms, circa 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 51)
        - Matchbook cover, circa 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 51)
        - Vehicle marking guides, circa 1977-1978 (Box 51)
      - [Storyboard, undated; removed to Box 63.] (Box 51)
      - Typeface studies/sketches, circa 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Butterworth Inc., design guide/logo studies, 1980, (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - CCMI McGraw-Hill
      - Corporate identity redesign, presentation boards, circa 1984, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - Q-Tel 1000 Guide, advertisement sketch/dog photograph, circa 1984 (Box 52)
    - Check Card Systems/Entre International (Interchec, Excheqr), corporate identity program
      - Final presentation boards (check, credit card, folder designs), circa 1965 (Box 52)
      - Letterhead/Logo designs, circa 1965 (Box 52)
      - Storyboard, Rough presentation for two to four minute strip with color and sound, circa 1965 (Box 52)
    - Creative Tools Inc., Easydriver screwdriver packaging/promotional sketches, undated (Box 52)
    - Exxon/Esso (Box 53)
      - Presentation boards/materials
        - Exxon Office Systems (EOS), circa late 1970s
          - Presentation 1: Photographs, Sign/Office Models, Sketches, undated, (3 folders; 1 folder removed to Box 63.) (Box 53)
          - Presentation 2: Branch Offices, Reception Areas, Overall Sign Recommendations, undated, (3 folders) (Box 53)
          - Signage studies (Box 54)
            - Blueprint, 1981 (Box 54)
            - Final presentation boards, undated (Box 54)
            - Sketches, undated (Box 54)
          - Various boards, undated, (2 folders) (Box 54)
        - Name Development Project, undated, (2 folders) (Box 54)
        - Uniflo gasoline, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - Food Fair Stores (Box 55)
      - Cheq-List presentations, circa 1972, (2 folders) (Box 55)
      - Storyboards, circa 1972 (Box 55)
    - Gilbarco (Box 56)
      - Logo (company mark/logotype), circa 1960s (Box 56)
      - Presentation boards
        - Corporate identity program (regional offices, gas pumps, promotion), circa 1960s, (2 folders) (Box 56)
        - International regional offices/corporate organization charts, circa 1960s (Box 57)
        - Vehicle designs (Gilbarco Canada, Australia, Brazil, Suisse), circa 1960s (Box 57)
      - Typeface samples, undated (Box 57)
    - Jeffrey Furniture catalog, New Designs in Business Furniture, 1965 (Box 58)
    - John H. Muller & Associates brochure, Research Center at Stevens (Hoboken, N.J.), undated (Box 58)
    - North American Reinsurance Corporation
      - Advertisement proofs, When Opportunity Knocks campaign, 1970s (Box 58)
      - Alphabet designs and logo announcement, undated (Box 58)
      - Letterhead, circa 1975-1978, (3 folders) (Box 58)
      - Master mechanical art logo, circa 1975-1978, (2 folders) (Box 59)
      - Presentation, undated (Box 59)
      - Transparencies, circa 1975-1978, (2 folders; 1 folder removed to Box 63.) (Box 59)
      - Typography, undated (Box 59)
    - Richardson-Vicks (formerly Richardson-Merrill), newsletter designs, 1977-1978 (Box 60)
    - Russ Berrie, letterhead and logo designs, 1973-1974, (3 folders) (Box 60)
    - Tishman Realty and Construction, property brochures/mailings
      - Bromley Hall (Ohio University), circa 1960s (Box 60)
      - Gateway Towers (Pittsburgh, Penn.), circa 1960s (Box 60)
      - Horizon House (N.J.), circa 1960s (Box 60)
      - Tower East (New York, N.J.), circa 1960s (Box 60)
  - Oversize Materials
    - Corporate Identity Programs and Paper Records
      - Equitable Life Assurance, Gateway Center (Pittsburgh, Penn.) booklet, 1964 (Box 61)
      - Exxon/Esso Identification Guide, 1965 (Box 61)
      - John F. Kennedy memorial document, circa 1964 (Box 62)
      - Kasandra, logo concepts, circa 1987 (Box 62)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, newsletter, 1970 (Box 62)
      - Morgan Press Collection at the Smithsonian, circa 1989, (4 folders) (Box 62)
    - Presentations, Sketches and Architectural Models
      - American Loose Leaf, storyboard, undated (Box 63)
      - Exxon Office Systems, presentation, undated (Box 63)
      - North American Reinsurance Corporation, transparencies, circa 1975-1978 (Box 63)
- Photographic Materials Series, 1946-1990 and undated [RESTRICTED], (3 boxes)
  Primarily documents graphic design projects completed for corporate clients including Exxon/Esso, Gilbarco, IBM, Philip Morris, and Russ Berrie. Some slides correspond to three-dimensional packages in the Graphic Design Series, for clients including Art Crayon Company, Asgrow-Mandeville, Dorset Laboratories, and Standard Brands. Also contains photographs of typographical artifacts (Arabic, Chinese, Greek, Persian) used for the book Type and Typography, as well as slides used for Ben Rosen Associates promotional presentations and for book project promotion. Arranged in three categories--negatives, photographs, and slides--and alphabetically therein by client or subject.
  - Negatives (CLOSED)
    Prints do not exist for all negatives.
    Restrictions on access: Negatives are closed to researchers. Consult research services about the availability of use prints.
    - Books (Box 64)
      - Corporate Search for Visual Identity, Type and Typography, book covers and promotion, undated (Box 64)
      - Type and Typography, Classic Pages manuscripts, undated (Box 64)
    - Clients
      - Barton's holiday candy, 1956 (Box 64)
      - IBM (632 model), cube design, contact sheet/negatives, circa 1955-1957 (Box 64)
      - Philip Morris, package concepts, circa 1960s (Box 64)
      - Sargent, Color Festival, undated (Box 64)
      - Various packaging (Royal Sweden, Royal Flan, Will-Hold rollers), undated, (2 folders) (Box 64)
    - UPC symbol/Postal reply bar codes, 1990 and undated (Box 64)
  - Photographs
    - Ben Rosen Associates (Box 65)
      - Ben Rosen with Alan Friedoerg (Montclair Imports), circa 1960s (Box 65)
      - Office (drafting tables), circa 1950s (Box 65)
      - Portraits, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 65)
    - Books
      - Type and Typography, Classic Pages, 1963-1985 and undated, (6 folders) (Box 65)
        Includes photographs of Greek, Arabic, Mesopotamian, Egyptian, Chinese, French, and Persian stone sculptures/artifacts/inscriptions. Artifacts date from the ninth century B.C.E. through the twentieth century C.E. Photographs originally obtained from the Library of Congress, the Pierpont Morgan Library, the Metropolitan Museum of Art, and the American Museum of Natural History.
    - Clients (graphic design and packaging)
      - Art Crayon Company, colored chalk, 1959 (Box 65)
      - Barton's holiday candy box, 1956 (Box 65)
      - Ben-Mont Papers
        - Art-Craft holiday gift wrap displays, undated (Box 65)
        - Display/Road signs, undated (Box 65)
      - Coats & Clark, 1957-1958 (Box 65)
      - Equitable Life Assurance Company, Gateway Building, circa 1965-1967 (Box 65)
      - Exxon/Esso, gas station models/mock-ups, 1980, (2 folders) (Box 65)
      - IBM 632 model, cube design/promotion, circa 1955-1957 (Box 65)
      - International Standard Brands, circa early 1970s (Box 65)
      - Karo syrup, undated (Box 65)
      - Marvella Pearls, 1949 (Box 65)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, publications, circa late 1960s (Box 65)
      - Montclair Imports
        - Dinalon lotion, undated (Box 65)
        - Royal Sweden brushes, Wil-hold magnetic rollers, undated (Box 65)
      - Philip Morris
        - Packaging for chewing tobacco (Old Delft, Field and Stream), circa 1960s
          - Cigarettes
            - Benson & Hedges (Parliament, Virginia Rounds, Stag cigarettes; Royal Amber tobacco), circa 1960s (Box 65)